[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[海鸥的叫声]
?THEME SONG: Are you ready, kids
主题曲：孩子们，准备好了吗
!Aye, aye, Captain
！是啊是啊，队长
!I can't hear you
！我听不到你说话
!Aye, aye, Captain
！是啊是啊，队长
!Ooooh
！哦哦
Who lives in a
?pineapple under the sea
谁住在一个
?海底菠萝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
Absorbant and yellow
.and porous is he
吸水性和黄色
.他是多孔的
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
If nautical nonsense
.be something you wish
如果航海废话
.成为你想要的东西
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
Then drop on the deck
.and flop like a fish
然后落在甲板上
.然后像鱼一样扑通扑通
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
?Ready
？准备好
,SpongeBob SquarePants
,海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
[GUFFAWS]
[狂笑]
NARRATOR: Here we are
again at the Bikini
旁白：我们到了
再次在比基尼
.Bottom Boating School
.底划船学校
Today is, once again, the day
of SpongeBob's boating school
今天，又是这样的日子
海绵宝宝的划船学校
.exam
。考试
But more importantly, this is
.the last test for the year
但更重要的是，这是
.今年最后一次测试
And if SpongeBob does
,not pass this one
如果海绵宝宝这么做了
,过不了这一关
it means another whole
!year of boating school
这意味着另一个整体
！划船学校的一年
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
[GROANS]-
[呻吟]-
?What happened
？发生了什么
.Oh, nothing, SpongeBob-
.哦，没什么，海绵宝宝-
You just struck
.another pedestrian
你刚刚击中
.另一个行人
.Minus 20 more points
.再减20分
How many does-
?that leave me with
有多少个——
？这让我
.Negative 224-
.负224-
How many more minutes-
?left in the test
还有多少分钟——
？留在测试中
.The test is over-
.测试结束了-
.That's enough time-
.时间够了-
!I can make up those points
！我可以弥补这些要点
.No, SpongeBob-
.不，海绵宝宝-
!Wait
！等待
.You didn't hear me
.你没听见我说话
!Aah
！啊啊
!It's too late, SpongeBob
！太晚了，海绵宝宝
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
[COUGHS]
[咳嗽]
,OK, Mrs. Puff-
?what's my final score
，好吧，普芙夫人——
?我的最终成绩是多少
.6-
!Whoo-
！呼——
?And how many do I need to pass-
？我需要通过多少项-
.Six-
。六-
--Whoo-
--呼呼-
.Hundred-
。百-
?What-
？什么-
.600-
.You need 600 to pass
.你需要600才能通过
.You got 6
.你有6个
.Don't worry-
。不用担心-
.I'll be all right, Mrs. Puff
.我会没事的，普夫夫人
Besides, this means
that I get to be
除此之外，这意味着
我会成为
in your class for a
.whole 'nother year
在你的班级里
.又一年
.Well, see you next Tuesday
.好吧，下周二见
!Yeah
！是的
SINGING) I'm going to)
.get my driver's licence
唱歌）我要去）
.取得我的驾驶执照
And it's only going
.to take one more year
而且它只会继续
.再花一年时间
.One more year
.还有一年
.One more super-duper year
.又是超级骗局的一年
,One my super-spectacular
,extra-magical
,我的一个超级壮观
,超神奇的
.extra-fantastical year
.超凡脱俗的一年
:(MRS. PUFF (VOICEOVER
!Oh, Neptune
:(普芙夫人（画外音）
！哦，海王星
.Another year with him
.又和他在一起一年
!Barnacles
！藤壶
!Dirty barnacles
！肮脏的藤壶
I've got to do something
.to save myself
我必须做点什么
.为了拯救我自己
.Huh, there's only one way out
.呵呵，只有一个出路
.A teacher's ace in the hole
.老师的王牌
!Extra credit-
!额外学分-
?What was that, Mrs. Puff-
？那是什么，普芙夫人——
.Extra credit, SpongeBob-
.额外积分，海绵宝宝-
.The extra credit
.额外学分
.LAUGHS] I still have a chance]
.笑]我还有机会]
I-- I mean, you
.still have a chance
我——我是说，你
.还有机会
?What's extra credit-
?什么是额外的学分-
It's when you get-
credit for the things
就是当你得到——
对事物的信用
.you weren't able to do before
.你之前做不到
!SINGING) Ooooh)-
！唱歌）哦哦）-
Now, are we ready-
?for that extra credit
现在，我们准备好了吗——
？为了额外的学分
.Extra credit-
.额外学分-
.That's the spirit-
.这就是精神-
So all you have to do to
earn your extra credit
所以你所要做的就是
赚取额外学分
and pass my class and never
have to come anywhere near
并通过了我的课程，但从未
this school again is write
a 10-word sentence on what
这所学校又是写
关于什么的 10 个词的句子
you've learned in
.boating school
你已经学到了
.划船学校
But I've learned-
.so many things
但我已经学会了——
.很多事情
.Just pick one-
.只选一个-
.I don't care which
.我不在乎哪个
.Here, I'll help you get started
.在这里，我将帮助您开始
What I learned in boarding"
!school is"-- there
我在寄宿中学到的东西”
！学校在”——那里
.That's already seven words
.这已经是七个字了
!Only three more
！只剩下三个了
--"L-E-A-R"-
--“L-E-A-R”-
[PENCIL SNAPS]
[铅笔快照]
!Oh, barnacles
！哦，藤壶
?What's wrong-
？怎么了-
.Got to sharpen my pencil-
.得削我的铅笔-
[WHISTLES]
[口哨声]
.Hm
.嗯
[HUMMING]
[嗡嗡声]
?Hm
？嗯
[HUMMING]
[嗡嗡声]
--"N-E"
--“N-E”
[PENCIL SNAPS]
[铅笔快照]
!Oh
！哦
[WHISTLES]
[口哨声]
!Give me that-
！给我那个-
.Here's a pen
.这是一支笔
!A pen-
！一支笔——
One of the most permanent
.of all writing utensils
最永久的之一
.所有书写用具
.SINGING) Gonna write an essay)
.唱歌）要写一篇文章）
.That's what I say
.这就是我说的
!There
！那里
.Fantastic-
。极好的-
.Let me see it
.让我看看
!No, wait-
！不，等等——
!I've changed my mind
！我改变主意了
I'm sure what you've-
.written is fine
我确定你已经-
.写得很好
.Just let me see
.让我看看
!No, don't look-
！不，别看——
.It's not ready
.还没准备好
!It's so simple, only 10 words-
！就这么简单，只有10个字——
What I learned"
in boating school
我学到了什么”
在划船学校
!is"-- Blankety, blankety, blank
!is"--毯子，毯子，空白
!I can do this-
！我可以做到这一点-
!I can do this
！我可以做到这一点
FRANTIC) "What I learned)-
".in boating school is
疯狂）“我学到了什么）-
“.在划船学校是
What I learned in"
".boating school is
我在《中学到了什么》
“.划船学校是
!I can do this-
！我可以做到这一点-
I can do this! [PANTING] Is
?it hot in here, Mrs. Puff
我可以做到这一点！ [气喘吁吁]是
？这里很热，普夫夫人
GASPING] Why is]
?it so hot in here
喘气]为什么是]
？这里太热了
!Aah
！啊啊
!My hand
！我的手
!My hand is cramping, Mrs. Puff
！我的手抽筋了，普芙女士
!Make it stop
！让它停止
!You only need three more words-
！你只需再多说三个字——
!Ugh
！啊
OK, let me see what
.you've written
好的，让我看看是什么
.你已经写了
.It's not ready yet-
.还没准备好-
.That's OK, SpongeBob-
.没关系，海绵宝宝-
Show the teacher
.what you've written
给老师看
.你写的
!No-
！不-
!Give it to me-
！给我——
!No-
！不-
!Let me see it-
！让我看看-
What I learned in"
,boarding school is," uhh
我在《中学到了什么》
，寄宿学校是，”呃
.well, the rest doesn't matter
.好吧，其余的并不重要
!You've passed
！你已经通过了
!LAUGHS] You pass]
！笑]你通过了]
Mrs. Puff, I don't feel-
.like I really did anything
帕芙女士，我不觉得——
.就像我真的做了什么一样
That's how extra credit-
.is supposed to feel
这就是额外的信用——
.应该感觉
?Really-
？真的-
.Besides, here's your licence-
.此外，这是你的驾照-
.My licence-
.我的执照-
It tastes just like
.I dreamt it would
味道就像
.我梦想它会
--Mrs. Puff, I
- 太太。噗噗我
.MRS. PUFF: Thank you, SpongeBob
。太太。泡芙：谢谢你，海绵宝宝
.Congratulations
.恭喜
.Have a nice life
.祝你生活愉快
!Look out, Bikini Bottom-
！小心，比基尼泳裤-
.There a new driver on the road
.路上有新司机
And his name is
!SpongeBob SquarePants
他的名字是
!海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
SINGING) La la)
!la la la la la la
唱歌）啦啦）
！啦啦啦啦啦啦
--La la la lala
——啦啦啦啦啦
!Aah-
！啊啊——
!Ow-
！噢-
!SINGING) La la la la la la)-
！唱歌）啦啦啦啦啦啦）-
.La la la lala
.啦啦啦啦啦
!FISH: Ouch
!鱼：哎哟
!PARTYGOERS: There he is
!派对常客：他在那儿
!Happy birthday
！生日快乐
--SINGING) La la la la la la)-
--唱歌）啦啦啦啦啦啦）-
[THUDS]
[轰鸣声]
[GRUNTS]
[咕噜声]
.So much destruction-
.如此多的破坏-
?This reporter asks, why
？记者问，为什么
Local consensus places the
,blame on this negligent
地方共识将
,都怪这个疏忽
selfish driving
!instructor who-- oof
自私驾驶
！教练谁——噢
HALTINGLY) Let's)
.not use that take
犹豫地）让我们）
.不使用那个镜头
.That's preposterous-
.这太荒谬了-
.He did the extra credit
.他做了额外的功劳
[CHUCKLES]
[笑声]
.There's no need to worry
.无需担心
He doesn't even have
.a boat to drive
他甚至没有
.驾驶一艘船
Now, to go home and have
.the rest of that pasta
现在，回家去
.剩下的意大利面
[CHUCKLES]
[笑声]
!Aah
！啊啊
!ALL: Surprise
!ALL：惊喜
!To the greatest teacher ever-
！致有史以来最伟大的老师——
.Thank you, Mrs. Puff-
.谢谢你，普芙女士-
I know I speak for everyone
when I say that we consider you
我知道我代表所有人
当我说我们考虑你时
a member of the
.SquarePants family
的成员
.方裤家族
[LONG KISSING SOUND]
[长吻声]
I think you've made-
.your point, dear
我想你已经做到了——
.你的观点，亲爱的
.Ahem-
.咳咳-
Mrs. Puff, we were
starting to think SpongeBob
泡芙女士，我们是
开始思考海绵宝宝
was never going to
.get his licence
从来没有打算
.获得他的执照
.But you never gave up on him
.但你从未放弃过他
.You never quit
.你从未放弃
.You never took the easy way out
.你从来没有采取简单的出路
.Well, I, uh, OK-
.好吧，我，呃，好吧-
.We wanted to make sure Mrs-
Puff, the greatest driving
.我们想确保夫人-
泡芙，最伟大的驾驶
,teacher in the world
.was here to see this
,世界上的老师
.来这里是为了看到这个
?See what-
？看看什么-
!Ta-da-
！哒哒哒
".IM-RDY"
“.IM-RDY”
!BOTH: A brand-new boat-mobile
!BOTH：全新的移动船
?For me-
？为我-
.Ooh
.哦
[SPLAT]
[啪]
.Don't worry, Mrs. Puff-
.别担心，普夫夫人-
.He'll be driving by tomorrow
.他明天开车过来
!Toodle-loo
！涂鸦厕所
?What have I done-
？我做了什么-
Everyone will know that I
.let him slide through school
大家都会知道我
.让他顺利通过学校
I'll have to move
to a new city, start
我得搬家
到一个新的城市，开始
a new boating school
.with a new name
一所新的划船学校
.用新名字
.No, not again
.不，不再是
I've got to end this
.thing before it begins
我必须结束这一切
.开始之前的事情
You took quite a-
.buster there, son
你花了相当多的时间-
.巴斯特在那里，儿子
What I learned in-
!boating school today is
我学到了什么——
！今天划船学校是
We're going to have to-
hold off on the driving
我们必须——
暂停驾驶
.there for a while, son
.儿子，在那儿一段时间
.That's right, honey-
.没错，亲爱的-
.Now, just stay in bed
.现在，就躺在床上吧
.And no going near the boat
.并且不要靠近船
[DOOR SHUTS]
[门关上]
.Hi, Boaty-
.嗨，船蒂-
.GASP] Boaty, you're cold]
.GASP] Boaty，你好冷]
.Take my socks
.拿走我的袜子
Oh, Boaty, I'm always
.going to take care of you
哦，船蒂，我总是
.会照顾你的
You're the best boat
.in the deep blue sea
你是最好的船
.在深蓝色的大海里
[SIGHS]
[叹气]
I hope I still-
.remember how to do this
我希望我仍然——
.记住如何做到这一点
.Yeah
。是的
[SPONGEBOB: [SNORING
[海绵宝宝：[打鼾
!Hey
！嘿
.I'm driving
.我正在开车
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[两人都尖叫]
?Who are you
?你是谁
And what are you
?doing in my boat
而你又是什么
？在我的船上做
And why are you wearing that ski
?mask because you're not skiing
你为什么穿着那块滑雪板
？面具因为你不滑雪
!Oh, my gosh
！哦，天哪
!I know who you are
！我知道你是谁
.No, you don't-
.不，你不-
.You don't know who I am
.你不知道我是谁
!Yes, I do-
！是的，我愿意-
I know that you're
!a boat-jacker
我知道你是
！一个劫船者
I never thought I had to
.use this pepper spray
我从没想过我必须这样做
.使用这个胡椒喷雾
[SHRIEKS]
[尖叫声]
!Somebody help me
！有人帮助我
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
Sorry, SpongeBob, but-
.it was for your own good
对不起，海绵宝宝，但是——
.这是为了你好
[PANTING]-
[气喘吁吁]-
!Give me back my boat
！把我的船还给我
!You better stop this boat
！你最好停下这艘船
!I'm not letting go
！我不会放手
!Nothing will stop me
！没有什么能阻止我
?"Not even-- "giant clams
？“甚至没有——”巨蛤
!Ow
！噢
!No
！不
!Stop
！停止
!Ah
！啊
!Oh
！哦
!Ow
！噢
I'm not letting
!go even for-- huh
我不让
！甚至去 - 呵呵
?"Cheese graters"
？“奶酪刨丝器”
!No
！不
!Ow
！噢
!No
！不
!Stop
！停止
!No
！不
!Stop
！停止
!Ai
！人工智能
!Oh, no
！哦，不
If you think I'll
let go for a little
如果你认为我会
放开一点
?"educational television"
？“教育电视”
!Oh, no
！哦，不
!Aah
！啊啊
.Looks like that got rid of him-
.看起来这摆脱了他-
.Now, for some tunes
.现在，播放一些曲子
:(SPEAKER (ON RADIO
And now back to KRUD
:(扬声器（在广播中
现在回到克鲁德
with all of your
personal "you won't
与你的一切
个人“你不会
get away with
.stealing my car" hits
摆脱
.偷我的车”热播
!Aaah-
！啊啊——
[TYRES SCREECHING]
[轮胎尖叫声]
[GRUNTS]
[咕噜声]
.Hey, look-
.嘿，看-
[BOTH SHRIEKING]
[两人都尖叫]
!Oof-
！钱币-
!Oof
！钱币
!Arg
！精氨酸
I'd never let you
!have this boat
我永远不会让你
！有这艘船
--Not even if you were
——即使你是
[GASP]
[喘气]
?Mrs. Puff--
？太太。噗 -
[SIREN]
[警笛]
?So how's it going, Mrs. Puff-
？怎么样，帕芙女士——
Uh, SpongeBob, I'd-
.like to apologise
呃，海绵宝宝，我会-
.想道歉
.I shouldn't have passed you
.我不应该超越你
.You really weren't ready
.你真的还没准备好
So I guess I got to give-
?my licence back, huh
所以我想我必须给-
？我的驾照回来了，嗯
.I hear Mrs-
Flounder is starting
.我听到夫人-
比目鱼开始了
.a new class Monday morning
.周一早上新课
?You kidding-
？你开玩笑吧-
You're the only teacher
.for this student
你是唯一的老师
.对于这个学生
And besides, the warden
says she'll let you
除此之外，典狱长
说她会让你
.go early if you do her a favour
.如果你帮她一个忙就早点去
?What's that-
？那是什么-
.Free driving lessons-
.免费驾驶课程-
[LAUGHS]
[笑]
!SPONGEBOB: Wow
！海绵宝宝：哇
!I can't believe it
！我简直不敢相信
We're actually here at the
.Biannual Jellyfish Convention
我们实际上在这里
.一年两次的水母大会
.Jellyfish are awesome-
.水母真棒-
Cool state-of-the-art-
.jellyfish nets
酷炫的先进技术——
.水母网
.Touch-
。触碰-
.Don't touch-
.别碰-
!Wow-
！哇-
The harpoon from
".Jellyfish, the Movie"
鱼叉来自
“.水母，电影”
.Touch-
。触碰-
.Don't touch-
.别碰-
Look, Dr. Manowar, the guy-
who got stung by Big Lenny
瞧，马诺瓦尔博士，那个人——
谁被大莱尼蛰了
.and lived
.并且生活过
And now, it only hurts when-
!you touch it. (BAWLING) Ow
而现在，只有当——
！你触摸它。 （嚎叫） 噢
.Touch-
。触碰-
Do I have to-
?follow you all day
我必须-
?整天跟着你
!SHRIEKING] Patrick, look]-
！尖叫]帕特里克，看]-
?Can it be
？可以吗
?Ice cream-
？冰淇淋-
,No, it's the Jellyspotters-
Bikini Bottom's
，不，是 Jellyspotters——
比基尼泳裤
premier jellyfish
.enhusiasts' club
顶级水母
.爱好者俱乐部
!Ah
！啊
And their leader, the coolest
,jellyfish enthusiast ever
还有他们的领袖，最酷的
,曾经的水母爱好者
.Kevin the Sea Cucumber
.凯文海参
What's so great-
?about a nerdy pickle
有什么了不起的——
？关于书呆子泡菜
If I could just touch the-
,hem of his pocket protector
如果我能触碰——
,他的口袋保护器的下摆
then maybe some of his
.greatness would rub off on me
那么也许他的一些
.伟大会感染我
SpongeBob, as a friend, I-
.most say that's really geeky
海绵宝宝，作为朋友，我——
.大多数人说这真的很怪异
!GASP] Oh, my gosh]
！喘息]哦，天哪]
!Jeffrey Jellyfish
！杰弗里水母
!Wa-wa-- wait, Jeffrey
！哇哇——等等，杰弗里
!I have to touch you
！我必须触碰你
!Hey-
！嘿-
?Bamboo-
？竹子-
I only use composite
.materials in my net handle
我只使用复合
.materials 在我的网络句柄中
?CROWD: Composite materials
?CROWD：复合材料
--Composite
- 合成的
.Next question-
.下一个问题-
.CROWD: Next question
.CROWD：下一个问题
.Next question
.下一个问题
.Uhh, hi, Kevin-
.呃，嗨，凯文-
.Hi-
。你好-
?What is your question
?你的问题是什么
.Hi, Kevin-
.嗨，凯文-
.Whatever-
。任何-
.Next question, please
.请下一个问题
.Hi, Kevin-
.嗨，凯文-
.Hello, loser-
.你好，失败者-
.All right, you, way in the back
.好吧，你，在后面
.Hi, Kevin-
.嗨，凯文-
Does anyone here-
--have an actual
这里有人吗——
——有一个实际的
[HEAVY BREATHING]-
[粗重的呼吸声]-
.Hi, Kevin
.嗨，凯文
.I'm your biggest fan
.我是你最大的粉丝
.You're too kind-
.你太善良了-
!Security
！安全
!No, wait-
！不，等等——
!I would do anything for you
！我愿意为你做任何事
Why don't you go-
?jump off a building
你为什么不走-
？跳楼
[SPONGEBOB: [SCREAMING
[海绵宝宝：[尖叫
?Huh-
？哈-
[CRASH]
[碰撞]
.Anything-
。任何事物-
.Punch yourself in the face-
.打自己的脸-
?Doesn't that hurt you
？这不会伤害你吗
Do you want it-
?to hurt me, Kevin
你想要吗-
？伤害我，凯文
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
!That is the best-
！这样最好了——
[LAUGHS]
[笑]
.This guy's great
.这家伙很棒
We have got to bring this
.guy jellyfishing with us
我们必须带这个
.guy 和我们一起钓水母
.No, Kevin, no-
.不，凯文，不-
.He's a geek
.他是个极客
Look, I won't let the-
.guy to join the club
听着，我不会让-
.guy加入俱乐部
I just want to see how
many times he can get stung
我只是想看看如何
很多时候他会被蜇
before he goes running
.home like a baby
在他跑步之前
.像婴儿一样回家
.Meep-meep-
.咪咪咪-
.Kevin's a genius
.JELLYSPOTTERS: Meep-meep-meep
.凯文是个天才
.JELLYSPOTTERS：喵喵喵
.Kevin's a genius
.凯文是个天才
.Genius
。天才
.Kevin
.凯文
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
.Kevin
.凯文
Hey, kid, how would you like to-
?try out for the Jellyspotters
嘿，孩子，你想怎样——
?尝试 Jellyspotters
[LONG BEEP]
[长鸣声]
.Clear-
。清除-
!I'd love it-
！我会喜欢的-
.Hm-
.嗯-
!Ah-
！啊-
Nothing like driving
through jellyfish fields
没有什么比开车更重要的了
穿过水母田
,with the top down
?hey, Jellyspotters
,自上而下
？嘿，Jellyspotters
.JELLYSPOTTERS: Meep
.JELLYSPOTERS：米普
.Top down
。自顶向下
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
.Top down
。自顶向下
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
.Ah-
。啊-
.Oh, here we are
.哦，我们到了
.Jellyfish Fields
.水母田
!GROANS] Dah]
！呻吟] 啊]
I hope you didn't-
.forget our nets
我希望你没有-
.忘记我们的网
.I didn't forget them, Kevin-
.我没有忘记他们，凯文-
.They're in the trunk
.它们在后备箱里
I can't believe I'm out
.here with the Jellyspotters
我不敢相信我已经出去了
.与 Jellyspotters 一起
I mean, all my life, I
.wanted to be a Jellyspotter
我的意思是，我一生
.想成为 Jellyspotter
And now, I'm out here with
you guys with the nets
现在，我和
你们这些有网的人
.and the jars and the jellyfish
.And I'm with Kevin
.还有罐子和水母
.我和凯文在一起
.And Kevin's with me
.And we're all with each other
.凯文和我在一起
.我们都在一起
.And we're jellyfishing together
.And it's fun
.我们一起捉水母
.而且很有趣
--And I'm
——而我是
!Hold it-
！坚持住——
Before you become
,a Jellyspotter
在你成为之前
,果冻发现者
you have to pass
.a rigorous test
你必须通过
.严格的测试
:JELLYSPOTTERS
.LAUGHING] Rigorous test]
：果冻观察员
.Laughing]严格的测试]
--Test
- 测试
!Quiet-
！安静的-
!Sh
！嘘
--You're first test
.catch a jellyfish
--你是第一个测试者
.捕捉水母
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
.Hey, I caught one-
.嘿，我抓到了一个——
?Am I a jellyspotter now
？我现在是果冻观察者了吗
.JELLYSPOTTERS: Meep
.He caught one
.JELLYSPOTERS：米普
.他抓到了一只
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
.Oh, that doesn't count-
.哦，这不算——
!Ouch
！哎哟
.SPEAKER: Wah-wah-wah
.发言者：哇哇哇
.I meant two jellyfish-
.我的意思是两只水母-
,Two jellyfish-
.meep, in the net
,两只水母-
.meep，在网络中
.JELLYSPOTTERS: Meep, in the net
.JELLYSPOTTERS：Meep，在网中
.Jellyfish in net
.网中的水母
.Th-- that's not what I meant-
.Th--我不是这个意思-
.I meant 20 jellyfish
.我的意思是20个水母
.Oh, uh, let's see-
.哦，呃，让我们看看-
--One, two, three
- 一二三
!Oh, beat it-
！哦，打败它-
!Ow
！噢
[YELLS]
[喊叫]
.SPEAKER: Wah-wah-wah
.发言者：哇哇哇
Jellyspotters allow jellyfish-
.to eat jelly off their face
Jellyspotters 允许水母——
.吃掉脸上的果冻
?Who wants to lick my cheeks-
？谁想舔我的脸颊-
.I see I have some takers
.我发现我有一些接受者
?How does it feel-
?感觉如何-
[LAUGHING]-
[笑]-
.It tickles my nose
.它让我的鼻子发痒
.Not for long-
.不会长久-
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
!SPONGEBOB: Ah, hah, hahchoo
!海绵宝宝：啊哈哈哈哈哈哈
!Wah-wah-wah-
！哇哇哇-
?Will you cut that out-
？你能把那个删掉吗-
?Am I in the Jellyspotters now-
？我现在是 Jellyspotters 中的人吗？
.No-
。不-
I have many more
.tests for you to take
我还有很多
.测试供您参加
?Am I in the Jellyspotters now-
？我现在是 Jellyspotters 中的人吗？
[ZAP]
.No-
。不-
?Am I in the Jellyspotters now-
？我现在是 Jellyspotters 中的人吗？
[ZAP]
!No-
！不-
?Now-
？现在-
[ZAP]
!No-
！不-
?Now-
？现在-
[ZAP]
!No-
！不-
?Now-
？现在-
[ZAP]
!No-
！不-
?Now-
？现在-
[ZAP]
?Now
？现在
[ZAP]
?Now-
？现在-
[ZAP]
OK, SquarePants, it is-
.your turn to get zapped
好吧，方裤，是——
.轮到你被攻击了
I mean, are you ready
?for your final test
我的意思是，你准备好了吗？
？为了你的最终测试
!I'm ready-
！我准备好了-
You'd better be-
because we are going
你最好是——
因为我们要去
.to capture a queen jellyfish
.捕捉女王水母
?A queen-
？女王-
?Can I help
？我可以帮忙吗
.Oh, don't worry-
.哦，别担心-
.We can't do it without you
.没有你我们做不到
.This is fantastic-
.这太棒了-
.I've never been bait before
.我以前从来没有当过诱饵
I don't think I've ever seen
.a queen jellyfish either
我想我从来没有见过
.女王水母
Well, then you probably never-
.used a queen jellyfish call
好吧，那么你可能永远不会-
.使用了水母女王的叫声
?Why don't you try it out
？你为什么不尝试一下呢
.BOOMING) Loser)-
.BOOMING）失败者）-
.Loser
.失败者
Hey, I've heard
.this call before
嘿，我听说过
.此调用之前
.I'll bet you have-
.我敢打赌你有-
?Hey, where are you going-
？嘿，你要去哪里-
.Oh, don't worry-
.哦，别担心-
.We'll be right behind this bush
.我们就在这片灌木丛后面
[ZAPS]
!Ow
！噢
?Who's got my sting ointment
?谁有我的蜇伤药膏
!This is great-
！这太棒了-
When I pass this test, I'll be
.an official jellyfish spotter
当我通过这个测试时，我会
.官方水母观察员
.BOOMING) Loser)
.BOOMING）失败者）
.Loser
.失败者
.WEAKLY) Loser)
.弱）失败者）
Hey, Kevin, I don't
.think it's working
嘿，凯文，我不
.认为它有效
.Nothing
。没有什么
!Hey
！嘿
!Hey, Kevin
！嘿，凯文
.She's here
.她在这里
.Look, look, she's here
.看，看，她来了
.She's here
.她在这里
.She's here, Kevin
.她在这里，凯文
--She
- 她
[GASP]
[喘气]
[ZAPS]
!Aah
！啊啊
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
[ZAPS]
!Aah
！啊啊
Please don't be
.angry, Your Highness
请不要
.生气了，殿下
.I would have let you go
.我本来会让你走的
[BAWLING]
[嚎叫]
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
[GASPS]
[喘气]
!Kevin
！凯文
.That's right-
。这是正确的-
You should have seen the look
.on your face when we zapped you
你应该见过这个样子
.当我们攻击你时在你脸上
?But what about my final test-
？但是我的最终测试呢-
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
Did you think we'd actually-
?let you join the Jellyspotters
你以为我们实际上会-
？让你加入 Jellyspotters
But, Kevin, I was-
.you the biggest fan
但是，凯文，我是——
.你是最大的粉丝
.So were they-
.他们也是——
.Hey, look, everybody-
.嘿，看，大家-
!Kevin's back
！凯文回来了
!FANS: Kevin
！粉丝：凯文
!We love you, Kevin
！我们爱你，凯文
!Kevin's here
！凯文来了
You look so dumb with-
!your dorky jellyfish call
你看起来很蠢-
！你那傻乎乎的水母叫声
!Loser
.JELLYSPOTTERS: Meep
！失败者
.JELLYSPOTERS：米普
.Loser
.失败者
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
.Loser
.失败者
!Loser-
!失败者-
.I am not a loser-
.我不是失败者-
!Looooser-
！Loooser-
！松点-
!Loser
！失败者
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
?Huh
？哈
!Cnidaria Rex
! 刺胞动物
.King Jellyfish-
.王水母-
.Rrrowrr-
.Rrrrrrr-
.呜呜呜-
.Mmmwah
.嗯哇
!Kissyface-
！亲亲脸-
[PANTING]-
[气喘吁吁]-
?Hhrrh-
？呼呼——
!Kevin
！凯文
[ZAPS]
[YELLS]
[喊叫]
[WHISTLES]
[口哨声]
[GASPS]
[喘气]
.I think he's gone-
.我想他已经走了-
.One of you go out and check
.你们中的一个人出去检查一下
.Meep-meep-
.咪咪咪-
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
[ZAP]
!Aah
！啊啊
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
!meep-meep
.JELLYSPOTTERS: Meep
.JELLYSPOTERS：米普
.Save us
.拯救我们
.Meep
.米普
.Save us
.拯救我们
.Kevin, save us
.凯文，救救我们
--Save us
——拯救我们
.Don't look at me-
.别看着我-
I was just in this
.for the fashion
我刚刚在这
.为了时尚
.It's hopeless
.没希望了
!We're trapped
！我们被困住了
.We're trapped
.我们被困住了
!Help me, Mommy
！帮帮我，妈妈
!Help me
！帮我
!I want my blankie
！我想要我的毯子
?Now, what do we do-
？现在，我们做什么-
JELLYSPOTTERS: Um, help
.me, Mommy, Mommy, Mommy
JELLYSPOTTERS：嗯，帮忙
.我，妈妈，妈妈，妈妈
.Help, Mommy, Mommy, Mommy
.救命，妈妈，妈妈，妈妈
.Help
。帮助
--Help
- 帮助
[GROWLING]-
[咆哮]-
?What the
？什么？
!Hmm-
！唔-
.Mm, mm, mm
.毫米、毫米、毫米
.Yummy
.美味
[CHEERING]
[欢呼]
.Meep-meep-
.咪咪咪-
.Meep-meep
.米普米普
.I can't believe it-
.我简直不敢相信-
?How did you know
？你怎么知道的
!LAUGHS] Everybody loves pie]-
！笑]每个人都喜欢馅饼]-
.Wah-wah-wah-
.哇哇哇-
,Well, SquarePants-
.that was impressive
，好吧，方裤-
.这令人印象深刻
But you're still not
in the club because you
但你仍然不是
在俱乐部因为你
.didn't catch a queen jellyfish
.没有捕获女王水母
?Wait, what are you doing
？等等，你在做什么
[RIPS]
[撕裂]
!Aah
！啊啊
!Wow-
！哇-
.I didn't know this was a hat
.我不知道这是一顶帽子
.It wasn't-
.这不是-
.SPONGEBOB: Hi, Patrick
.海绵宝宝：嗨，帕特里克
.Hi, SpongeBob-
.嗨，海绵宝宝-
?Did you get into that club
？你加入那个俱乐部了吗？
.Yeah, but I turned them down-
.是的，但我拒绝了他们-
.It's not about Kevin
.这不是关于凯文
.It's about jellyfish
.这是关于水母的
SpongeBob, I'm glad-
.you learned your lesson
海绵宝宝，我很高兴——
.你吸取了教训
.Hero worship is unhealthy
.英雄崇拜是不健康的
.Come on, Jeffrey
.来吧，杰弗里
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]